{
    "subject": "resource/The_Bronze_Buckaroo",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English-language_films",
    "human_readable": "The Bronze Buckaroo is about English-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.974284827709198,
            "question": "Does 'The Bronze Buckaroo' focus on a particular genre of English-language films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9555875658988953,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres of English-language films covered by 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9542945623397827,
            "question": "What language are the films featured in 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.93864905834198,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the history of English-language films based on 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9346776008605957,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the cultural impact of English-language films based on 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8718445301055908,
            "question": "Can you find information about specific movies in 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.823700487613678,
            "question": "Is 'The Bronze Buckaroo' about documentaries or fictional films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7782137989997864,
            "question": "What is the topic of 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7278797030448914,
            "question": "Does 'The Bronze Buckaroo' include information about the directors or actors of these films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6723596453666687,
            "question": "What makes 'The Bronze Buckaroo' unique compared to other resources about films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Bronze Buckaroo is about English-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7201_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does 'The Bronze Buckaroo' include information about the directors or actors of these films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7201_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the topic of 'The Bronze Buckaroo'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7201_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Bronze Buckaroo' about documentaries or fictional films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7201_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7201_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that the film \"The Bronze Buckaroo\" is in the English language, which supports the statement that it is about English-language films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe provided context clearly mentions that the film \"The Bronze Buckaroo\" was produced with English as its language. Therefore, it supports the statement that \"The Bronze Buckaroo is about English-language films.\""
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The film does not specify the language as English; it only mentions the language as English within the context is an assumption, and there is no confirmation that the film's original language is English.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The film's language is explicitly stated as English.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}